{
     "quiz1": [{
               "question": "5 + 7 = ? (from quiz 1)",
               "choices": [
                    "10",
                    "11",
                    "12",
                    "13"
               ],
               "answer": "12"
          },
          {
               "question": "12 - 8 = ?",
               "choices": [
                    "1",
                    "2",
                    "3",
                    "4"
               ],
               "answer": "4"
          },
          {
               "question": "3 + 1 = ?",
               "choices": [
                    "10",
                    "11",
                    "4",
                    "13"
               ],
               "answer": "4"
          },
          {
               "question": "10 - 2 = ?",
               "choices": [
                    "1",
                    "2",
                    "8",
                    "4"
               ],
               "answer": "8"
          },
          {
               "question": "5 + 11 = ?",
               "choices": [
                    "10",
                    "11",
                    "16",
                    "13"
               ],
               "answer": "16"
          },
          {
               "question": "1 - 8 = ?",
               "choices": [
                    "1",
                    "-7",
                    "3",
                    "4"
               ],
               "answer": "-7"
          },
          {
               "question": "1 + 3x = ?",
               "choices": [
                    "1",
                    "4",
                    "7",
                    "15"
               ],
               "answer": ["1", "4", "7"]
          },
          {
               "question": "1 + 2x = ?",
               "choices": [
                    "1",
                    "3",
                    "2",
                    "5"
               ],
               "answer": ["1", "3", "5"]
          },
          {
               "question": "5x + 0 = ?",
               "choices": [
                    "5",
                    "10",
                    "15",
                    "12"
               ],
               "answer": ["5", "10", "15"]
          },
          {
               "question": "20x - 1 = ?",
               "choices": [
                    "-1",
                    "19",
                    "20",
                    "39"
               ],
               "answer": ["-1", "19", "39"]
          }
     ],

     "quiz2": [{
               "question": "5 + 7 = ? (from quiz 2)",
               "choices": [
                    "10",
                    "11",
                    "12",
                    "13"
               ],
               "answer": "12"
          },
          {
               "question": "12 - 8 = ?",
               "choices": [
                    "1",
                    "2",
                    "3",
                    "4"
               ],
               "answer": "4"
          },
          {
               "question": "3 + 1 = ?",
               "choices": [
                    "10",
                    "11",
                    "4",
                    "13"
               ],
               "answer": "4"
          },
          {
               "question": "10 - 2 = ?",
               "choices": [
                    "1",
                    "2",
                    "8",
                    "4"
               ],
               "answer": "8"
          },
          {
               "question": "5 + 11 = ?",
               "choices": [
                    "10",
                    "11",
                    "16",
                    "13"
               ],
               "answer": "16"
          },
          {
               "question": "1 - 8 = ?",
               "choices": [
                    "1",
                    "-7",
                    "3",
                    "4"
               ],
               "answer": "-7"
          },
          {
               "question": "1 + 3x = ?",
               "choices": [
                    "1",
                    "4",
                    "7",
                    "15"
               ],
               "answer": ["1", "4", "7"]
          },
          {
               "question": "1 + 2x = ?",
               "choices": [
                    "1",
                    "3",
                    "2",
                    "5"
               ],
               "answer": ["1", "3", "5"]
          },
          {
               "question": "5x + 0 = ?",
               "choices": [
                    "5",
                    "10",
                    "15",
                    "12"
               ],
               "answer": ["5", "10", "15"]
          },
          {
               "question": "20x - 1 = ?",
               "choices": [
                    "-1",
                    "19",
                    "20",
                    "39"
               ],
               "answer": ["-1", "19", "39"]
          }
     ],
     "quiz3": [{
               "question": "5 + 7 = ? (from quiz 3)",
               "choices": [
                    "10",
                    "11",
                    "12",
                    "13"
               ],
               "answer": "12"
          },
          {
               "question": "12 - 8 = ?",
               "choices": [
                    "1",
                    "2",
                    "3",
                    "4"
               ],
               "answer": "4"
          },
          {
               "question": "3 + 1 = ?",
               "choices": [
                    "10",
                    "11",
                    "4",
                    "13"
               ],
               "answer": "4"
          },
          {
               "question": "10 - 2 = ?",
               "choices": [
                    "1",
                    "2",
                    "8",
                    "4"
               ],
               "answer": "8"
          },
          {
               "question": "5 + 11 = ?",
               "choices": [
                    "10",
                    "11",
                    "16",
                    "13"
               ],
               "answer": "16"
          },
          {
               "question": "1 - 8 = ?",
               "choices": [
                    "1",
                    "-7",
                    "3",
                    "4"
               ],
               "answer": "-7"
          },
          {
               "question": "1 + 3x = ?",
               "choices": [
                    "1",
                    "4",
                    "7",
                    "15"
               ],
               "answer": ["1", "4", "7"]
          },
          {
               "question": "1 + 2x = ?",
               "choices": [
                    "1",
                    "3",
                    "2",
                    "5"
               ],
               "answer": ["1", "3", "5"]
          },
          {
               "question": "5x + 0 = ?",
               "choices": [
                    "5",
                    "10",
                    "15",
                    "12"
               ],
               "answer": ["5", "10", "15"]
          },
          {
               "question": "20x - 1 = ?",
               "choices": [
                    "-1",
                    "19",
                    "20",
                    "39"
               ],
               "answer": ["-1", "19", "39"]
          }
     ],
     "quiz4": [{
               "question": "5 + 7 = ? (from quiz 4)",
               "choices": [
                    "10",
                    "11",
                    "12",
                    "13"
               ],
               "answer": "12"
          },
          {
               "question": "12 - 8 = ?",
               "choices": [
                    "1",
                    "2",
                    "3",
                    "4"
               ],
               "answer": "4"
          },
          {
               "question": "3 + 1 = ?",
               "choices": [
                    "10",
                    "11",
                    "4",
                    "13"
               ],
               "answer": "4"
          },
          {
               "question": "10 - 2 = ?",
               "choices": [
                    "1",
                    "2",
                    "8",
                    "4"
               ],
               "answer": "8"
          },
          {
               "question": "5 + 11 = ?",
               "choices": [
                    "10",
                    "11",
                    "16",
                    "13"
               ],
               "answer": "16"
          },
          {
               "question": "1 - 8 = ?",
               "choices": [
                    "1",
                    "-7",
                    "3",
                    "4"
               ],
               "answer": "-7"
          },
          {
               "question": "1 + 3x = ?",
               "choices": [
                    "1",
                    "4",
                    "7",
                    "15"
               ],
               "answer": ["1", "4", "7"]
          },
          {
               "question": "1 + 2x = ?",
               "choices": [
                    "1",
                    "3",
                    "2",
                    "5"
               ],
               "answer": ["1", "3", "5"]
          },
          {
               "question": "5x + 0 = ?",
               "choices": [
                    "5",
                    "10",
                    "15",
                    "12"
               ],
               "answer": ["5", "10", "15"]
          },
          {
               "question": "20x - 1 = ?",
               "choices": [
                    "-1",
                    "19",
                    "20",
                    "39"
               ],
               "answer": ["-1", "19", "39"]

          }
     ]
}